
// All questionIds should start from 0.
export const satQuestions = [
    {
        type: "SAT",
        subType: "Math",
        questionId: 0,
        question: "What is \$1 + 1\$?",
        answer: "2",
        choices: [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4",
        ],
    },
    {
        type: "SAT",
        subType: "Math",
        questionId: 1,
        question: "What is 1 - 1?",
        answer: "0",
        choices: [
            "0",
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
        ],
    },
    {
        type: "SAT",
        subType: "Math",
        questionId: 2,
        question: "In the complex number system, which of the following is equal to \$(14 - 2i)(7 + 12i)\$?",
        answer: "122 + 154i",
        choices: [
            "74",
            "122",
            "74 + 154i",
            "122 + 154i",
        ],
    },
    {
        type: "SAT",
        subType: "Math",
        questionId: 3,
        question: "At a primate reserve, the mean age of all the male primates is \$15\$ years, and the mean age of all female primates is \$19\$ years. Which of the following must \
            be true about the mean age \$m\$ of the combined group of male and female primates at the primate reserve?",
        answer: "15 < m < 19",
        choices: [
            "m = 17",
            "m > 17",
            "m < 17",
            "15 < m < 19",
        ],
    },
    {
        type: "SAT",
        subType: "Math",
        questionId: 4,
        question: "The function \$f\$ is defined by \$f(x) = 2x^3 + 3x^2 + cx + 8\$ where \$c\$ is a constant. In the \$xy\$-plane, the graph of \$f\$ intersects the \$x\$-axis at the \
        three points \$(-4, 0), (1/2, 0)\,$ and \$(p, 0)\$. What is the value of \$c\$?",
        answer: "-18",
        choices: [
            "-18",
            "-2",
            "2",
            "10",
        ],
    },
    {
        type: "SAT",
        subType: "Science",
        questionId: 5,
        question: "    Unmanned spacecraft taking images of Jupiter’s moon Europa have found its surface to be very smooth with few meteorite craters. Europa’s surface ice shows evidence of being continually resmoothed and reshaped. Cracks, dark bands, and pressure ridges (created when water or\
            slush is squeezed up between 2 slabs of ice) are commonly seen in images of the surface. Two scientists express their views as to whether the presence of a deep ocean beneath the surface is responsible for Europa’s surface features.\
            \
            Scientist 1\
            \
            A deep ocean of liquid water exists on Europa. Jupiter's gravitational field produces tides within Europa that can cause heating of the subsurface to a point where liquid water can exist. The numerous cracks and dark bands in the surface ice closely resemble the appearance of thawing ice covering the polar oceans on Earth. Only a substantial amount of circulating liquid water can crack and rotate such large slabs of ice. The few meteorite craters that exist are shallow and have been\
            smoothed by liquid water that oozed up into the crater from the subsurface and then quickly froze.\
                Jupiter’s magnetic field, sweeping past Europa, would interact with the salty, deep ocean and produce a second magnetic field around Europa. The spacecraft has found evidence of this second magnetic field.\
            \
            Scientist 2\
                No deep, liquid water ocean exists on Europa. The heat generated by gravitational tides is quickly lost to space because of Europa’s small size, as shown by its very low surface temperature (–160°C). Many of the features on Europa’s surface resemble features created by flowing glaciers on Earth. Large amounts of liquid water are not required for the creation of these features. If a thin layer of ice below the surface is much warmer than the surface ice, it may be able to flow and cause cracking and movement of the surface ice. Few meteorite craters are observed because of Europa’s very thin atmosphere; surface ice continually sublimes (changes from solid to gas) into this atmosphere, quickly eroding and removing any craters that may have formed.\
            \
            Based on the information in Scientist 1’s view, which of the following materials must be present on Europa if a magnetic field is to be generated on Europa?",
        answer: "Dissolved salts",
        choices: [
            "Frozen nitrogen",
            "Water ice",
            "Dissolved salts",
            "Molten magma"
        ],
    },
];

// All questionIds should start from 1000.
export const actQuestions = [
    {
        type: "ACT",
        subType: "Math",
        questionId: 1000,
        question: "What is 1 + 4?",
        answer: "5",
        choices: [
            "2",
            "3",
            "4",
            "5",
        ],
    },
    {
        type: "ACT",
        subType: "Math",
        questionId: 1001,
        question: "What is 1 - 1?",
        answer: "0",
        choices: [
            "0",
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
        ],
    },
    {
        type: "ACT",
        subType: "English",
        questionId: 1002,
        question: "What is a synonym for happy?",
        answer: "Joyful",
        choices: [
            "Joyful",
            "Sad",
            "Mad",
        ],
    },
];

// All questionIds should start from 2000.
export const apQuestions = [
    {
        type: "AP",
        subType: "Calculus BC",
        questionId: 2000,
        question: "Compute the integral \$  \\frac{1}{\sqrt{\pi}} \int_{-\\infty}^{\\infty} e^{-x^2} \\text{d}x.\$",
        answer: "1",
        choices: [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4",
        ],
    },
    {
        type: "AP",
        subType: "Calculus BC",
        questionId: 2001,
        question: "\$\lim_{x \\to \\infty} \\frac{\sqrt{9x^4+1}}{x^2-3x+5}\$ is",
        answer: "3",
        choices: [
            "1",
            "3",
            "9",
            "nonexistent",
        ],
    },
    {
        type: "AP",
        subType: "Calculus BC",
        questionId: 2002,
        question: "A rain barrel collects water off the roof of a house during three hours of heavy rainfall. The height of the water in the barrel increases at the rate of \$r(t) = 4t^3e^{-1.5t}\$ \
        feet per hour, where \$t\$ is the time in hours since the rain began. At time \$=1\$ hour, the height of the water is \$0.75\$ foot. What is the height of the water at time \$t=2\$ hours?",
        answer: "1.361 ft",
        choices: [
            "1.361 ft",
            "1.500 ft",
            "1.672 ft",
            "2.111 ft",
        ],
    },
    {
        type: "AP",
        subType: "World History",
        questionId: 2003,
        question: "When was The Israel Agundis born?",
        answer: "2000",
        choices: [
            "1999",
            "2000",
            "2001",
        ],
    },
    {
        type: "AP",
        subType: "World History",
        questionId: 2004,
        question: "In the eighteenth century, which of the following contributed most directly to the\
        change in the volume of silver trade on the Southern African route?",
        answer: "The expanded activities of chartered and joint-stock companies",
        choices: [
            "The development of new types of ships, such as the caravel and the carrack",
            "The expanded activities of chartered and joint-stock companies",
            "The conversion of the rulers of west African states to Christianity",
            "The discovery of gold and diamonds in southern Africa"
        ],
    }
];


// All questionIds should start from 3000
export const codingQuestions = [
    {
        type: "CODING",
        subType: "Frontend",
        questionId: 3000,
        question: "Which is a frontend framework?",
        answer: "React",
        choices: [
            "React",
            "Python",
            "SQL",
            "Loops",
        ],
    },
    {
        type: "CODING",
        subType: "Backend",
        questionId: 3001,
        question: "Which language is used to perform queries?",
        answer: "SQL",
        choices: [
            "Java",
            "Python",
            "SQL",
            "C++",
        ],
    },
];

export const allQuestions = [
    ...satQuestions,
    ...actQuestions,
    ...apQuestions,
    ...codingQuestions,
];
